Guide to the Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records, 1893-2008.
Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records
- Series IV. Cornell University Theatre and Cornell Dramatic Club
  - Scripts and Prompt Books
    - One-act plays for A. M. Drummond course, 1933-1938
      - "School for Doctors" by John R. Hefler; "The Sidewalk" by Beatrice Marks; "Progression" by Charles Brunelle; "Columnists Gather" by Franklin A. Moss (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - "Let Them Laugh!" by Homer E. Baker; "The Importance of Not Needing Women," "The First and the Last" and "The Unexpected Which Happens" by Lewis Freed; "A Portrait of Charles Baudelaire" and "A Count of No Account" by Ruth Press (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - "For the Honor of the Family," "Illusion" and "This New Independence" by E.M. McAdoo; "As One Having a Great Inheritance" and "The Way Out" (original and rewrite) by Mary K. Rogers (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - "Forgive and Forget," "No Interview Granted," "Youth Cures the World," "Three Years Robbed" and "A Babe in Time" by Leonard I. Feinstein (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - "For Us, the Living" by R. Heavey; "The Interior Decorator" by R.K. Ketcham; "Tangled" by Theodore Hatlen; "Birthday" by Julia Brainard Carson; "The Shop of Idols" by Peter Hancock; "Sweet Little Thing!" by Marjorie Bornholz; "Pass the Butter" by Alan F. Mock; "Thy Neighbor" by Howard Rogers Houston; "Vacation" by J. Clausen; "The House by the Side of the Road" by Annette R. Baker (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - "Marriage for Two," Paid in Full" and "Yet Each Man Kills" by Betty Mallabar; "Central Park Village," "Party at Sandor's" and "To Stonehenge" by Risa Lowie (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - "Green is the Grass," "Let It Be Forever Nameless" and the Treaty of the Pumpkins" by Rodney Stewart; "Interference" and "Lady Trouble" by Maude D. Baltzell; "The $10,000 Legacy," "Consolidation" and "Lessons" by Paul W. Hettes (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - "The Guild Meeting," untitled and "Poppy's Garden" by Frank H. Turner; "The Weaker One," "Family Man" and "The Coward's Dream" by Adrian Charles Spies (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - "Love - My Heart!," "Portrait of Washington," "Caesar Reigns," "A Lovesome Thing" and "What'll He Think or The Prince is Coming" by Amelia Ruxton; "The Wrong Mr. Wright," "The Doctor's Wife" and "Alias Chester Brown" by Mildred Hammond-Knowlton (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - "The Blood-Red Paint" and untitled by Virginia Campbell; "Mr. Bumpus," "Eve's Inner Core" and "Ladies, I Thank You!" by Dorothy Kaucher; "Jostling Jed," "A Pair of Dice" and "Compromise" by Ada Lefkowith (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - "Nothing Personal," "New York is not the Universe" and "Home is the Warrior" by Thelma Levine; "The Sins of the Father" and "Three Men are Killed" by Margaret Hopkins; "He's a Nice Boy" and "Waitress" by Dorothy Zitz; "Three Wishes," "A Miracle" and "A Few Regulations" by Dee Morrison Booth (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbooks and Memorabilia
    - Scrapbooks, 1909-1937; 4 volumes (Box 12)
    - Scrapbooks, 1936-1953; 4 volumes (Box 13)
    - Scrapbooks, 1953-1963; 3 volumes (Box 14)
    - Scrapbook, 1963-1965; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Scrapbook-Cornell University Theatre films, 1939-1943; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Scrapbooks, 1893/1894 - 1900/1901 (Box 1)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 2)
      Includes 1901/1902 - 1903/1904,1904-1911,1911-1921
    - Scrapbooks (Box 4)
      Includes 1908-1922, 1925/1926, 1922-1925, 1923/1924
      1925/1926 has 3 volumes.
    - Cornell Dramatic Club publicity, 1924-1925 (Box 4)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club scrapbook, 1908-1916 (Box 4)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club scrapbook, 1908-1916 (Box 35)
    - Loose photos, program from scrapbooks (Box 4)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 5)
      Includes 1926/1927, 1927/1928, 1928/1929
      1927/1928 has 3 volumes.
    - Scrapbooks (Box 6)
      Includes 1928/1929, 1930/1931, 1929/1930
      1930/1931 has 3 volumes. 1929/1930 has 2 volumes.
    - Scrapbooks, 1931/1932-1934/1935 (Box 7)
    - Scrapbooks, 1934/1935-1938/1939 (Box 8)
    - Scrapbooks, 1938/1939-1941/1943 (Box 9)
    - Scrapbooks, 1943/1944-1948/1959 (Box 10)
    - Scrapbooks, 1949/1950-1952/1956 (Box 11)
    - South America tour scrapbook, 1962 (Box 17)
    - Press book for Candida and Four New York State Plays, 1939 (Box 36)
    - Summer Theatre scrapbook, 1965 (Box 36)
    - Scrapbooks, 1962-1963 (Box 37)
    - Summer Theatre scrapbook, 1970-1978 (Volume 1)
    - Reviews and publicity scrapbook, 1971-1977 (Volume 2)
    - Metal embossing stamp for Dept. of Public Speaking, MU 390 (Box 51)
    - Cornell Women's Dramatic Club scrapbook, Circa 1914-1925 (Box 56)
      Includes stationary, programs, news-clippings, photographs, broadsides, correspondence from University officials accepting invitations, and "Report of the Committee on Amalgamation" concerning incorporation of Women's Dramatic Club into the Cornell Dramatic Club (May 25, 1925)
  - Programs, Posters and other Printed Materials
    - The Pirates of Penzance advertising poster (Mapcase-folder 1)
    - "The Chairs" and "Krapp's Last Tape" advertising poster, April 24-28 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    - Poster advertising Fin de Partie by Samuel Beckett, produced by le Theatrographe at the Theatre Saint-Jean (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Poster advertising plays at the Chaillot, Grand-Theatre, La Mama de New York, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - CU Theatre film posters (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Cornell dance concert posters (Mapcase-folder 6)
    - Ithaca Repertory Theatre posters (Mapcase-folder 7)
    - Pirates of Penzance, Ithaca Choral Club (Mapcase-folder 5)
    - CU Theatre, CDC posters (Mapcase-folder 5)
    - CU Theatre posters (Box 39, Folder 1-3)
    - CU Theatre posters, circa 1925-1963 (Box 41)
    - CU Theatre film and theater posters, circa 1925-1963 (Box 42)
    - Kita Noh Theater Company programs, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Regular and Summer Season Programs
      - An Enemy of the People, March 5, 1909 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - 1909-1910 Season
        - The Pillars of Society, December 16, 1909 (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - An Enemy of the People, April 2, 1910 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - 1910-1911 Season
        - The Inspector General, April 21, 1911 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - 1912-1913 Season
        - Dandy Dick, April 25, 1913 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - 1913-1914 Season
        - Miss Civilization; A Clerical Error, December 17, 1913 (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - The Garroters; A Bit of Instruction; A Romantic Comedy, March 13, 27, 1914 (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - A Clerical Error; Fritzchen; Press Cuttings, May 8, 1914 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - 1914-1915 Season
        - Like Falling Leaves, March 23, 1915 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - 1915-1916 Season
        - Like Falling Leaves, November 5, 1915 (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - L'Aventurier/The Adventurer, May 4, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - 1916-1917 Season
        - Between the Soup and the Savoury; Indian Summer; The Master of the House, January 12, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Feed the Brute; The Last Man In; By Ourselves, January 26-27, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - The Shadow of the Glen; The Post-Scriptum; Lonesome-Like, March 17, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Sabotage; A Game of Chess; Cathleen Ni Hoolihan, March 31, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Sabotage; A Game of Chess; Cathleen Ni Hoolihan, April 2, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Leonarda, April 23, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - 1917-1918 Season
        - Make-Believe; Riders to the Sea; Welsh Honeymoon, November 2, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - The Marriage Proposal; The Hour Glass; Modesty, November 22, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - Playgoers; The Work-House Ward; The Golden Doom, December 13, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - The Monkey's Paw; Joint Owners in Spain; Pariah; The Pot of Broth, April 12-13, 15, 1918 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - 1918-1919 Season
        - Between the Soup and the Savoury; A Game of Chess; The Traveling Man, December 13-14, 1918 (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - 'Op-o'-Me-Thumb; The Dear Departed; The Maker of Dreams, March 14-15, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Alice in Wonderland, March 14-15, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - The Clod; The Farewell Supper; The Ghost of Jerry Bundler, April 5, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Free Speech; The Bank Account; Her Tongue, May 17, 19, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - 1919-1920 Season
        - The Country Theater (The Neighbors; The Pot O' Broth; The Workhouse Ward; The Bracelet, September 8-13, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Where but in America; Sabotage; Lima Beans, February 26-28, 1920 (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Three Pills in a Bottle; The Fest of the Holy Innocents; The Wonder Hat, 1920 (Box 43, Folder 10)
          Includes April 30 and May 1
        - America Passes By; Sam Average; Behind the Beyond, May 28-29, 1920 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - 1920-1921 Season
        - Their Annual Blowout, 1920; Signatures on program (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - The Country Theater (The Neighbors; Lonesomelike; Joint Owners in Spain; The Zone Police; Food!), September 13-18, 1920 (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - Lonesomelike, The Neighbors, Joint Owners in Spain, November 12-13, 1920 (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - The People; The Sweeps of Ninety-Eight; Bird in Hand, December 10-11, 1920 (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - The One Way Out, February 16, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - The Boor; Aria da Capo; A Night at an Inn, March 17, 19, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - Close the Book; Tents of the Arabs; Behind the Beyond, May 6-7, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - Vaudeville, A la Mode, April 23, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - 1921-1922 Season
        - Country Theatre (A Night at an Inn; The Boor; Joint Owners in Spain; Feed the Brute; The Striker), September 12-17, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - Feed the Brute; A Night at an Inn; Everybody's Husband, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 12)
          Includes September 30 and October 1
        - Blind; Gringoire, the Ballad Monger; The Pot-Boiler, November 4-5, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - Spreading the News; Trifles; Monday, December 2-3, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - The Silver Lining; The Intruder; How He Lied to Her Husband, January 13-14, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - Counsel Retained; In the Zone; The Hall of Laughter, March 3-4, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - The Lost Silk Hat; The Goal; The Mouse Trap, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 12)
          Includes March 30 and April 1
        - The Diary; Soil; The Soul of a Professor, April 28-29, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - Original Plays: Betsey Anne; How Old is Alice; The Soul of a Professor, May 23-24, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - Senior Week (Her Heart Was Richer Than Gold; Feed the Brute; The Soul of a Professor; The Pot-Boiler), June 19, 1922; Produced with the Cosmopolitan Club and the Masque (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - 1922-1923 Season
        - Exile; Jilted; Out of the Night, October 20-21, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 13)
        - The Old Lady Shows Her Medals; Two Crooks and a Lady; Hearts; Two Slatterns and a King, December 1-2, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 13)
        - The Ghost Story; Fortune and Men's Eyes; The Hero of Santa Maria, December 15-16, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 13)
        - Bound East for Cardiff; In the Shadow of the Glen; The Man of Destiny, January 19-20, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 13)
        - The Bracelet; Fame and the Poet; The Love-You-Clock, March 15-16, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 13)
        - The Whiteheaded Boy, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 13)
          Includes March 31 and April 2-3
        - Love and Geography, April 27-28, 30, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 13)
        - A Game of Chess; The Last of the Lowries; Sir David Wears a Crown, May 11-12, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 13)
        - A Very Mixed Business, June 2, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - 1923-1924 Season
        - Thursday Evening; Riders to the Sea; Wurzel Flummery, October 26-27, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 14)
        - Monday; The Golden Doom; A Dollar, November 23-24, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 14)
        - The Neighbors; The Land of Heart's Desire; Behind the Beyond, December 14-15, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 14)
        - The Valiant; The Very Naked Boy; Miss Maria, January 18-19, 23 1924 (Box 43, Folder 14)
        - The Camberley Triangle; The Last Man In; The Trysting Place, March 14-15, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 14)
        - Arms and the Man, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 14)
          Includes April 29, May 1-3, June 13-14
        - Strife, May 16, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 14)
        - Cornell Dramatic Club Season 1923-24 (Box 43, Folder 14)
        - Lyceum Theatre: Violin Recital by Mischa Elman; The Parisian; Zander the Great, 1923-24 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Summer 1924
        - A Door Must Be Either Open or Closed; Riders to the Sea; Feed the Brute, July 11-12, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 15)
        - The Marriage Proposal; The Last Man In; Overtones, July 19-21, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 15)
        - Thursday Evening; The Very Naked Boy; Suppressed Desires, July 25-26, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 15)
        - Ever Young; Solemn Pride; Joint Owners in Spain, August 1-2, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 15)
        - Overtones; The Last Man In; Thursday Evening, August 4, 1924; Produced with The Exchange Club of Ithaca for a Boy Scouts benefit (Box 43, Folder 15)
        - Three Cornell Comedies (Forest Home; How Old is Alice?; The Soul of a Professor), August 7, 9, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 15)
        - Arms and the Man, August 12-14, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - 1924-1925 Season
        - The Storm; Never-the-less; Double Demon, October 17-18, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Cheezo; A Sunny Morning; The Hall of Laughter, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 16)
          Includes October 31 and November 1
        - The Hall of Laughter; Never-the-Less; Double Demon, November 8, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Where the Cross is Made; The Drawback; Where Do We Go From Here?, November 14-15, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Wappin' Wharf, November 21-22, 28-29, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Overtones; The Bogie Men; The Zealous Guardian, December 5-6, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Solemn Pride; A Matter of Husbands; The Man Who Married a Dumb Wife, December 11, 13, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - The Playboy of the Western World, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
          Includes January 16-17 and February 21
        - Junior Week (Double Demon; The Drawback; The Man Who Married a Dumb Wife; The Playboy of the Western World), February 6-7, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Ricardo and Viola; The Wash Tub, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
          Includes February 27-28 and March 6-7
        - The Far-Away Princess; The Dear Departed; The Trysting Place, March 13-14, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - The Inn of Discontent; Beauty and the Jacobin; The Pot Boiler, March 21, 23, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - The House Into Which We Are Born, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
          Includes March 27-28, 30 and May 1-2
        - Sabotage; His Widow's Husband; Feed the Brute, April 24, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Rain; The Love-You Clock; The Soul of a Professor, May 8, 11, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Gray Mists; Colonna; A Man Should Have a Wife, May 15-16, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Wappin' Wharf, June 12-13, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - The Valiant; The Stronger; A Matter of Husbands; Fancy Free, April 18, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - The Soul of a Professor, May 4, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Cornell Dramatic Club Season 1924-25, 1924-1925 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Summer 1925
        - Overtones; The Stronger; Feed the Brute, July 10-11, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - The Inn of Discontent; A Matter of Husbands; The Soul of a Professor, July 16, 18, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - The Last Man In; For Distinguished Service; Suppressed Desires, July 24-25, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - The Valiant; The Dear Departed; The Wash Tub, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 17)
          Includes July 30 and August 1
        - The Death of Tintagiles; The Neighbors; A Man Should Have a Wife, August 3, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - Riders to the Sea; The Drawback; A Minuet; Fancy Free, August 7-8, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - The Playboy of the Western World, August 11-13, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - 1925-1926 Season
        - Will o' the Wisp; The Workhouse Ward; The Glittering Gate, October 9-10, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - The Feast of the Holy Innocents; How He Lied to Her Husband; Bird in Hand, October 16-17, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Aria da Capo; Phipps; Thirty Minutes in a Street, October 23-24, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - The Ghost of Jerry Bundler; Wrong Numbers; Her Tongue, October 30-31, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Double Demon; A Minuet; The Zealous Guardian, November 6-7, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - The Contrast, November 19-21, 1925; The first play produced in the Willard Straight Hall theater. (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Napoleon's Barber; The Aulis Difficulty; The Dark Lady of the Sonnets, December 4-5, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Just Women; The Traitor; Acid Drops, December 8, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - The Second Shepherds' Play; Why the Chimes Rang, December 12, 15-16, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Wrong Numbers; A Matter of Husbands; The Glittering Gate; Never-the-less, January 9, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - A Woman of Character; Tents of the Arabs; X = O; A Seat in the Park, January 15-16, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - The Importance of Being Earnest, February 5-6, 12-13, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - The Shadow of the Glen; The Dumb and the Blind; The Medicine Show, February 19-20, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Cathleen ni Hoolihan; A Proposal Under Difficulties; Lima Beans, February 25, 27, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - It’s the Poor that 'Elps the Poor; Acid Drops; Thirty Minutes in a Street, March 5-6, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Young America; A Question of Principle; The Man in the Bowler Hat, March 12-13, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - The Sleeping Beauty, March 26-27, 1926; Freshmen women's play, Class of 1929 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - The Learned Ladies; The Forced Marriage, April 23-24, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Three Cornell Plays (Gestures; Sharp Practices; The Devil Comes to Town), 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
          Includes April 29 and May 1
        - Carnival; L'Ecole des Belles-Meres; Traffic Signals, May 7-8, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - The Stronger, May 13-15, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Mricchakatica (The Little Clay Cart), May 21-22, 1926; Produced with the Cornell Cosmopolitan Club (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - The Contrast, June 11-12, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Willard Straight Hall Map, November 18,1925 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Cornell Dramatic Club Season 1925-1926 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Summer 1926
        - Overtones; The Stronger; A Seat in the Park; Feed the Brute, July 9-10, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 19)
        - The Feast of the Holy Innocents; A Dollar; Thirty Minutes in a Street, July 15, 17, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 19)
        - Where the Cross is Made; How He Lied to Her Husband; A Matter of Husbands; Behind the Beyond, July 23-24, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 19)
        - Double Demon; Joint Owners in Spain; Fame and the Poet; X=O, July 29, 31, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 19)
        - Wrong Numbers; The Workhouse Ward; The Mousetrap; The Medicine Show, August 6-7, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 19)
        - The Man Who Married a Dumb Wife; Lima Beans; Traffic Signals, August 10-12, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 19)
        - Two Special Performances for the International Congress of Plant Sciences, August 17, 19, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - 1926-1927 Season
        - Where the Cross is Made; The Drawback; How He Lied to Her Husband; Fame and the Poet, October 1-2, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Scruples; The Green Scarf; A Pot o' Broth; The Very Naked Boy, October 8-9, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - The Eldest; The Marriage Proposal; Speaking to Father; Calpurnia's Dinner Party, October 15-16, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Freedom; A Night at an Inn; It Isn't Done; Free Speech, October 22-23, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Crabbed Youth and Age; Ever Young; The Magic of an Hour; The Mouse Trap, October 29-30, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Thomas Wilfred, November 5, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - So That's That; A Game of Chess; 'Op-o'-Me-Thumb; No Smoking, November 12-13, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Right You Are! (If You Think So), November 19-20, 25, 27, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Three Plays by Lord Dunsany (The Golden Doom; The Gods of the Mountain; The Glittering Gate), December 3-4, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Christmas Production (The Sheaphardes' Play; The Offering of the Sheaphardes; The Adoration of the Magi) from The Chester Mysteries, December 11, 13, 15, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Seven Keys to Baldpate, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 20)
          Includes January 14-15 and February 3-5
        - Shall We Join the Ladies?; Two Slatterns and a King; Behind the Beyond!, February 18-29, 25-26, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - The Critic, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 20)
          Includes March 4-5, 11-12, 18-19, and June 10-11
        - Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs, April 15-16, 1927; Freshmen women's play, Class of 1930 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - A Midsummer Night's Dream, April 22-23, 29-30, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Cornell Plays (The Door; A Tear for Harlequin; One of Cleopatra's Knights), May 6-7, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Cornell Plays (Bos'n; Rare Wine; Sappho's Lover), May 13-14, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Action; Traffic Signals, May 21, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Dramatica's Dinner Party of A Night at an Inn (Pot-Boiler), May 27, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Cornell Dramatic Club Season 1926-1927) (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Summer 1927
        - Wrong Numbers; The Very Naked Boy; A Seat in the Park; Lima Beans, July 8-9, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 21)
        - Riders to the Sea; Two Slatterns and a King; Monday; Action, July 14, 16, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 21)
        - The Neighbors; The Pot Boiler; Free Speech, July 22-23, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 21)
        - The Feast of the Holy Innocents; Acid Drops; Overtones; Thirty Minutes in a Street, July 28, 30, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 21)
        - His Widow's Husband; Etiquette; Suppressed Desires, August 5-6, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 21)
        - The Playboy of the Western World, August 9-11, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - 1927-1928 Season
        - By Their Words Ye Shall Know Them; The Bogie Men; The Daily Doesn't; Two Blind Men and a Donkey, October 7-8, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - Between Soup and Savoury; Rocking Chairs; The Wonder Hat, October 14-15, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - Ile; Pariah; The Pot Boiler, October 21-22, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - Release; The Lost Silk Hat; Rehearsal; Action, October 28-29, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - In the Zone, The Quod Wrangle, Evening Dress Indispensable, November 4-5, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - Gloria Mundi; Q; The Grand Cham's Diamond, November 11-12, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - The Jean Gros French Marionettes in The Adventures of Huck Finn and Tom Sawyer, November 17, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - The Jean Gros French Marionettes in The Blue Bird, November 17, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - Saved; Playgoers; The Grandmother; Monday, November 19, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - Outward Bound, 1927, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 22)
          Includes December 2-3, 1927; January 6-7, 1928
        - R.U.R. (Rossum's Universal Robots), January 13-14, 20-21, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - The School of Princesses, February 9-11, 17-18, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 22)